(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T12:30:21.284291",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ローソンへお越しの皆さん！
To everyone visiting Lawson!
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
Lawson campaign confirmed!
今回はこの6人が登場！
These 6 are appearing this time!
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
Details scheduled for release on March 9th!
菓子、カプセル玩具、雑貨、アミューズメント景品の新商品を初公開！
New merch for snacks, capsule toys, goods, and prizes premiering!
オリジナルフレームで撮影！あなただけのカードデザイン！
Snap photos with original frames! Your very own card design!
発売前のウエハースシリーズデザイン！？
Pre-release wafer series designs!?
ブースで限定カードがもらえる！
You can get a limited card at the booth!
And more! 最新プロジェクトも公開！
And more! Latest project also revealed!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
"Hey, it's because you were here."
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
"Hey, I want to say thank you over and over"
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
and tell you right now."
さあ乗れ込もう！
"Come on, let's hop on!"
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
"Wow oh oh..."
あぁ小さな夢から
"Ah, from a tiny dream,"
想像できないような
"into feelings so big"
想いになったんだ
we couldn't even imagine."
わくわく止まらない！
"Our excitement won't stop!"
何度迷ったって僕ら
"No matter how many times we got lost,"
絆が舵になる
"our bonds become the rudder."
ちょっとの不安だってさ
"Even a little bit of anxiety"
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
"we'll just blow it away!"
果てない旅路を今
"Now, on this endless journey"
航いでる途中に
"that we're navigating,"
困難もあるでしょう
"there are bound to be hardships,"
それも力に変えて
"but we'll turn those into strength"
一緒に進むんだよ！
"and move forward together!"
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
"Hey, it's because you were here."
ねぇ、夢では終われない
"Hey, we can't let it end just as a dream."
荒波も乗り越えていこう
"Let's ride over the rough waves together!"
“らしく”輝いていたい
"We want to shine in our own way."
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
"Hey, being able to meet you"
ねぇ、宝物だから
"Hey, is my treasure,"
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
"so let's hold hands, call out to each other,"
地図など無い未知の世界で
"and go even further in an uncharted world"
まだまだ行こう！
"with no map!"
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
"wow oh oh..."
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
"Even if sudden winds"
行く先乱そうとも
"try to disrupt where we're headed,"
あの日誓ったんだ
"the vow we made that day"
覚悟は揺るがない
"means our resolve won't waver."
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
"Backs telling us 'You've got to do it right!'"
明日への橋になる
"become a bridge to tomorrow."
もっと大事にしないとね
"We have to cherish things even more,"
“あたりまえ”は無いから
"because nothing can be taken for granted."
小さな船から始まるストーリー
"A story starting from a small boat,"
どっから始めればいいかもがいて
"struggling over where best to begin,"
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
"bit by bit forming a circle and finding"
何にも代えられない夢だ
"a dream that can't be replaced by anything."
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
"love even the incomplete,"
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
"our feelings are as one."
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
"even with just a glimmer of hope,"
僕と君でずっと
"you and I will keep going"
馬鹿にされても信じたい！
"and believe, even if mocked!"
ねぇ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
"Hey, 'thank you' isn't enough,"
ねぇ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
"hey, my feelings are overflowing."
ずっと一緒だよ！
"We'll be together forever!"
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
"Hey, it's because you were here."
ねぇ、夢では終われない
"Hey, we can't let it end just as a dream."
荒波も乗り越えていこう
"Let's ride over the rough waves together!"
“らしく”輝いていたい
"We want to shine in our own way."
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
"Hey, being able to meet you"
ねぇ、宝物だから
"Hey, is my treasure,"
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
"so let's hold hands, call out to each other,"
地図など無い未知の世界で
"and go even further in an uncharted world"
まだまだ行けるから！
"since we can still go on!"
ひとりじゃない
"You're not alone,"
何度でも立ち上がってさ
"stand up no matter how many times,"
笑い合っていたい
"and let's laugh together."
願いだってさみんなで、さあ！
"That's everyone's wish—come on!"
手を繋いで想像も超えて
"Holding hands, surpassing even imagination,"
まだまだ行こう！
"let's go even further!"
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
"wow oh oh..."
hey!! (hey!!)
yeah!!
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
"Hey, it's because you were here."
ねぇ、ありがとうを何度も
"Hey, I want to say thank you over and over"
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
"and tell you right now."
さあ乗れ込もう！
"Come on, let's hop on!"
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
"wow oh oh..."
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
"Ah, from a tiny dream,"
想像できないような
"into feelings so big"
想いになったんだ
"we couldn't even imagine."
わくわく止まらない！
"Our excitement won't stop!"
何度迷ったって僕ら
"No matter how many times we got lost,"
絆が舵になる
"our bonds become the rudder."
ちょっとの不安だってさ
"Even a little bit of anxiety"
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
"we'll just blow it away!"
果てない旅路を今
"Now, on this endless journey"
航いでる途中に
"that we're navigating,"
困難もあるでしょう
"there are bound to be hardships,"
それも力に変えて
"but we'll turn those into strength"
一緒に進むんだよ！
"and move forward together!"
ねぇ、君がいたからだよ
"Hey, it's because you were here."
ねぇ、夢では終われない
"Hey, we can't let it end just as a dream."
荒波も乗り越えていこう
"Let's ride over the rough waves together!"
“らしく”輝いていたい
"We want to shine in our own way."
ねぇ、君と会えたことが
"Hey, being able to meet you"
ねぇ、宝物だから
"Hey, is my treasure,"
手を取り合い 声かけ合って
"so let's hold hands, call out to each other,"
地図など無い未知の世界で
"and go even further in an uncharted world"
まだまだ行こう！
"with no map!"
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
"wow oh oh..."
hey!! hey!!
yeah!!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were here...
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
right away.
さあ乗り込もう！
Now let's hop on!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!!(hey!!)
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah!!
ああ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
into a feeling we couldn't even imagine,
想いになったんだ
it turned out this way.
わくわく止まらない!
Our excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we lost our way,
絆が舵になる
our bond becomes the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we'll blow it all away.
果てしない旅路を今
Now on this endless journey,
軽いている途中に困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be difficulties along the way,
それも力に変えて
but turning even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ!
let's move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were here...
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride out the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
Wanting to shine in our own unique way,
ねえ、君と会えたことが
hey, being able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
hey, is such a treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行こう!
let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
wow oh oh...
hey!!(hey!!)
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Sudden winds might try to disrupt
行く先乱そうとも
where we are headed,
あの日誓ったんだ
but we swore on that day
覚悟は揺るがない
our resolve will not waver.
きちんとしなくちゃ!って背中
"We've got to do things right!" that push on our backs
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなくちゃね
We need to cherish things even more,
“あたりまえ”はないから
because nothing can be taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat,
どっかから始めたらいいか悩んで
wondering where we should even begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
little by little, forming a circle, we found it.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
loving even our uncompleted selves.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
our feelings are one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
even with just a faint hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will always
馬鹿にされても
even if we are laughed at,
信じたい!
we want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough,
ねえ、想いが溢れ出してしまうんだよ
hey, my feelings are overflowing,
ずっと一緒だよ!
we'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were here...
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride out the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
Wanting to shine in our own unique way,
ねえ、君と会えたことが
hey, being able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
hey, is such a treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから!
we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
Getting back up no matter how many times
笑い合っていたい
and smiling together,
願いだってさみんなで、さあ!
that's our wish, everyone, come on!
手を繋いでイメージも超えて
Holding hands, going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう!
let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
wow oh oh...
hey!!(hey!!)
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah!!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were here...
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say "thank you" over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
right away.
さあ乗り込もう！
Now let's hop on!
ridin' on dreams
ああ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような
into a feeling we couldn't even imagine,
想いになったんだ
it turned out this way.
わくわく止まらない!
Our excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we lost our way,
絆が舵になる
our bond becomes the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety
吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
we'll blow it all away.
果てしない旅路を今
Now on this endless journey,
軽いている途中に困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be difficulties along the way,
それも力に変えて
but turning even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ!
let's move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, because you were here...
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, we won't let it end just as a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's ride out the rough waves together.
“らしく”輝いていたい
Wanting to shine in our own unique way,
ねえ、君と会えたことが
hey, being able to meet you
ねえ、宝物だから
hey, is such a treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map,
まだまだ行こう!
let's keep going further!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
wow oh oh...
hey!!(hey!!)
Hey!! Hey!!
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Sudden winds might try to disrupt
行く先乱そうとも
where we are headed.
これが星街再演サインぬい！！！！！！
This is Hoshimachi's encore signed plush!!!!!!
ローチケ当たってたので、、、解散かも？
Since I won the Lawson ticket... maybe we're disbanding?
声出せ！！
Make some noise!!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
マリン船長 400万人おめでとう
Congratulations to Captain Marine on 4M subscribers!
厳正なる抽選を行った結果 残念ながら今回はチケットをご用意することができませんでした
As a result of a rigorous lottery, unfortunately we could not prepare tickets for you this time.
声出して行くぞ
Let's make some noise!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
ロボ子さん
Robocosan
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
アキ・ローゼンタール
Aki Rosenthal
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
カエラ・コヴァルスキア
Kaela Kovalskia
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
オーロ・クロニー
Ouro Kronii
古石ビジュー
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravencroft
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
[Title: hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams]
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here,
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, thank you so many times,
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう!
Come on, let's get on board!
Ridin' on dreams
Yeah!!
ああ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream
想像できないような想いになったんだ
to feelings I couldn't have imagined,
わくわく止まらない!
the excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕らは 絆が舵になる
No matter how many times we get lost, our bond is the rudder.
ちょっとの不安だってさ 吹き飛ばしちゃうんだよ
Even a little anxiety, we can blow it away!
果てしない旅路を今 漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
On this endless journey, rowing along, there will be difficulties,
それも力に変えて
but turning that into strength too,
一緒に進むんだよ!
let's advance together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here,
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, it can't end in a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too,
“らしく”輝いていたい
wanting to shine "like myself."
ねえ、君と出会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you,
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, it's a treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Let's hold hands and call out to each other,
地図ない未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから!
because we can still go!
急な風が僕らの 行く先乱そうとも
Even if a sudden wind disrupts our destination,
あの日誓ったんだ 覚悟は揺るがない
we swore that day, our resolve won't waver.
「ちゃんとしなきゃ!」って背中
"I have to do it properly!" That back
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
I have to cherish it more,
“あたりまえ”はないから
because there is no "taken for granted."
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story that begins from a small boat,
どこから始めたらいいか悩んで
struggling with where to start,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
little by little, we formed a circle and found it.
何にも代えられない夢だ
It's a dream that cannot be replaced by anything!
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
love even the incomplete!
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
our feelings are one!
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
even if it's just a little hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I, forever,
馬鹿にされても
even if they make fun of us,
信じたい!
I want to believe!
ねえ、“ありがとう”じゃ足らない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough,
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing!
ずっと一緒だよ!
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here,
ねえ、夢では終わらせない
Hey, it can't end in a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too,
“らしく”輝いていたい
wanting to shine "like myself."
ねえ、君と出会えたことが
Hey, the fact that I could meet you,
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, it's a treasure.
手を取り合い声掛け合って
Let's hold hands and call out to each other,
地図ない未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map...
parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
It’s time to take the stage,
呼び合う声を合図に
I hear the voices calling out your name.
parade, parade, parade!
探しに行くスタートは何度だって
A new journey awaits,
ただ独り言を綴った
Just hit reset and we can start again.
ただ始まりたくて走った
Far away, lighting up all the darkness,
遠く暗がりに灯った
It’s a name, shining for us to notice.
それは眩し過ぎた名前
Memories that fill us up with kindness and love,
それは優し過ぎる思い出 もっと
Let’s surprise people who don’t know.
近づけると手を伸ばした
Every one that they called “the lost,”
思いがけず結び合った ほら 今
Here we are as “us”.
迷子は“僕等”になった
Parade, parade, parade!
parade, parade, parade!
It’s time to take the stage.
輝くんだよ
When disappointment gets in your way,
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいでで
Love will shine, keeping you safe.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てばさ
Feel the wind and wishes, your wings will take you high.
ささやかな祈りは光
These silent prayers will become our light,
終わりなき兆し
Guiding us on an endless flight.
君を見つけたこと
Finally, we found each other,
胸を張れるよ ここから これから
I can stand tall and say:
our bright parade, parade!
まだ頼りない予感を
We sing, full of uncertain feelings,
歌おう 恥ずかしかなんてないよ
We sing, and we’re not afraid of what they think.
誰も解けないイマジナリー
No one can decode what we’re imagining,
いつかまた逢えるおまじない
They don’t know our magic and our destiny.
あの日のゼロに始まったストーリー
When we met, this was an empty story, but now
数え切れない言の葉
Too many words to count them all out,
数えるような思いじゃないさ ほら 今
Feelings that leave no room for doubt,
“僕等”を
Take a look at where we are now,
一つと呼ぼう
All together as “one”.
parade, parade, parade!
美しいんだよ
It’s all so beautiful.
許し合える刹那
The moments of forgiveness shining,
夜はきらめく
Lighting up the darkest night.
雨、晴れ、カレイド
Rain or shine, I’ll treasure
またとない空
A kaleidoscope sky.
相応しい旅路とは
A journey that is made just for us,
君と在る事さ 君と有ることなんだ
And here I am, right by your side.
“ただいま”を聞けば
‘Cause there you are, standing by my side,
“おかえり”って叫ぶよ
When you’re back and open that door
当たり前じゃないか
You’ll hear us saying, “Welcome home”.
parade, parade, parade!
Forever we’ll be waiting.
輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade!
暗がりを満たすのは
It’s time to take the stage.
君だ僕だ!
We’re gonna shine right through the darkness,
parade, parade, parade!
Open up, share your light!
輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいでで
It’s time to take the stage.
風、夢、羽
When disappointment gets in your way,
飛び立てばさ
Love will shine, keeping you safe.
ささやかな祈りは光
Feel the wind and wishes, your wings will take you high.
終わりなき兆し
These silent prayers will become our light,
君と飛び込んでゆく
Guiding us on an endless flight.
素敵なスタートさ
Here I am ready to dive into
ここから ここから
A beautiful start with you.
our bright parade, parade!
Starting from here, starting right now,
parade, parade, parade!
輝くんだよ
It’s time to take the stage.
呼び合う声をアイズに
I hear the voices calling out your name.
parade, parade, parade!
探しに行く
A new journey awaits,
スタートは何度だって
Just hit reset and we can start again.
ただ独り言を綴った
Far away, lighting up all the darkness,
ただ始まりたくて走った
It’s a name, shining for us to notice.
遠く暗がりに灯った
Memories that fill us up with kindness and love,
それは眩し過ぎた名前
Let’s surprise people who don’t know.
それは優し過ぎる思い出 もっと
Every one that they called “the lost,”
近づけると手を伸ばした
Here we are as “us”.
思いがけず結び合った
Parade, parade, parade!
ほら 今 迷子は
It’s time to take the stage.
“僕等”になった
When disappointment gets in your way,
parade, parade, parade!
Love will shine, keeping you safe.
輝くんだよ
Feel the wind and wishes, your wings will take you high.
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいでで
These silent prayers will become our light,
風、夢、羽 飛び立てばさ
Guiding us on an endless flight.
ささやかな祈りは光
Finally, we found each other,
終わりなき兆し
I can stand tall and say:
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Starting from here, starting right now,
ここから これから
Our bright parade, parade!
our bright parade, parade!
We sing, full of uncertain feelings,
まだ頼りない予感を
We sing, and we’re not afraid of what they think.
歌おう 恥ずかしかなんてないよ
No one can decode what we’re imagining,
誰も解けないイマジナリー
They don’t know our magic and our destiny.
いつかまた逢えるおまじない
When we met, this was an empty story, but now
あの日のゼロに始まったストーリー
Too many words to count them all out,
数え切れない言の葉
Feelings that leave no room for doubt,
数えるような思いじゃないさ
Take a look at where we are now,
ほら 今 迷い込んだ
All together as “one”.
僕らは問題だった
Parade, parade, parade!
parade, parade, parade!
It’s all so beautiful.
輝くんだよ
The moments of forgiveness shining,
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいでで
Lighting up the darkest night.
風、夢、羽 飛び立てばさ
Rain or shine, I’ll treasure
ささやかな祈りは光
A kaleidoscope sky.
終わりなき兆し
A journey that is made just for us,
君を見つけたこと
And here I am, right by your side.
胸を張れるよ
‘Cause there you are, standing by my side,
ここから これから
When you’re back and open that door
our bright parade, parade!
You’ll hear us saying, “Welcome home”.
Forever we’ll be waiting.
君と歩くことさ
Walking along with you...
君と歩くことがなんだ
What is it to walk with you?
ただいまを聞けば
When I hear "welcome home"
おかえりってさ叫ぶよ
I shout back "welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that how it should be?
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's time to shine!
暗がりを充たすのは 君さ僕だ
What fills the darkness is you and me!
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, shine bright!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring your regrets and love along!
風、夢、羽 飛び立てばさ
Wind, dreams, wings, once you take flight
笹やかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
Quiet prayers become light, an endless sign,
君と飛び立っていく 素敵なスタートさ
taking flight with you, what a wonderful start!
ここから これから 変わらない パレパレ
From here, from now on, unchanging parade!
変わらない パレパレ
Unchanging parade, parade!
潰して すべてのステージを スタートです！
Crush every stage, and let's start!
What's up? One, two! Get out my way, so let's go!
言葉を選べ
Choose your words carefully
昨日の夜が明けて 壊せ、突き進む構造
Last night breaks into dawn, break the structure!
Break out! Break out! Break out! 分かってんだよ
Break out, break out, break out! I know it!
最後のステージだ！
This is the final stage!
鏡のように 怯える一週間分 嘘で染めた夜は
Frightened like a mirror for a week, nights dyed in lies
日々ジャックして 輝いた時に震えて
jack up the days, trembling when they shine
近づけてみたって この話はあなたに
Even if I tried to get close, this story is for you
君とはまるで違うって 分かったと ただこの嘘を眺めて
Realizing I'm different from you, gazing at this lie
#さがってばっかり 思い出してしまうのに 誤魔化してしまえるのは
Always backing down, even with memories, brushing them aside
確かにあった後悔から 誓ったんだ
I swore from regrets that were certainly there
さよなら 始まりのストーリーよ 光に包まれて
Goodbye, story of our beginnings, wrapped in light
触れられないほどに 揺れる意識をこんぱす
A compass for consciousness shaking so much I can't touch it
嘘で染めた夜は 日々ジャックして また揺らげるフライデー
Nights dyed in lies, jacking up the days, shaking Friday again
迷いは重ねた国 おもちゃを壊した正体
Hesitation is a layered country, the one who broke the toy
心を持った熱を 箱が照らす
The box illuminates the warmth that has a heart
#さがってばっかり 思い出してしまうのに 誤魔化してしまえるのは
Always backing down, even with memories, brushing them aside
大人になった後悔から 誓ったんだ
I swore from the regrets of becoming an adult
さよなら 最後の夜は さよなら 始まりのストーリーよ
Goodbye to our final night, goodbye to our starting story
選んで来た道のりは 今をずれておかしくしてしまう時が来ても
Even if the path I chose gets skewed and turns strange now
空に浮かぶ 次の光を見上げた
I looked up at the next light floating in the sky
虹を 道しるべにして 帰る場所
A place to return to, using the rainbow as a guide
#さがってばっかり 思い出してしまうのに 誤魔化してしまえるのは
Always backing down, even with memories, brushing them aside
確かにあった後悔から 誓ったんだ
I swore from regrets that were certainly there
光に触れるたびになってしまうよ My name is Palette
Every time I touch the light, it becomes My name is Palette!
どれも愛を模した TRUE
Every single one is a true imitation of love.
皆様！
Everyone!
この靴では
With these shoes,
獅子の後追い チュッチュッチュッでだよ
following the lion's footsteps with kisses!
待っててね！
Just wait for me!
リサ、もう
Lisa, already
破裂しちゃう！
peeling away!
抑えきれないの 私の頭がぐちゅぐちゅ知ってる
I can't hold back, my head knows it all messily.
冷たき瞳 尖る唇 無邪気な笑顔が
Uncaring eyes, pouty lips, innocent smiles—
もうとまらないの
I just can't stop anymore!
私の中の男子がぐずぐず続く
The boy inside me keeps crumbling down.
あふれ出しちゃう！
It's overflowing!
頭のてっぺんまでのびんびん感じちゃう
I feel it tingling all the way to my head!
熱くしっかりとよ のこのこじゃない
Burning and solid, not just casually strolling in.
かくれてないでよ 顔を見せて
Don't hide, show me your face!
風邪と病気の宝石箱 出力最大！
The jewelry box of colds, output at maximum!
見つけた！胸がギュンギュン愛は止まらないの
Found you! My heart is pounding, love won't stop!
好き好き大好き メリミー 私だけの お姫様 もう離さないずっと
Marry me, my only princess! I'll never let you go!
境界で意識を上げましょう 神様だって怖くない
Let's raise consciousness, even God isn't scary!
思い立ったが吉日じゃ お嫁に何卒チュッ！
Whenever you decide is lucky, please make me your bride!
お嫁に何卒チュッ！
Please make me your bride, muah!
退屈な日常 お帰りの際のご注意は？
What is the warning when returning from a routine?
さあて ごはんにしようかな お風呂にしようかな それとも…「私？」
Now then, dinner, a bath, or perhaps... me?
今日は二人で楽しそう、準備バッチリ？
Today we'll have fun together, ready?
ダニー、どこにいるの？
Danny, where are you?
もしかしてリサと隠れんぼしたいのかな？
Do you want to play hide-and-seek with Lisa?
テーブルの下？クローゼットの中かな？
Under the table? Inside the closet?
よしリサ、本気出しちゃうぞ！のばせ最大！
Alright Lisa, going all out! Extend to max!
甘いことのりずむ 赤い糸で二人つながっているのハートがびんびん
Sweet rhythm, connected by red string, hearts tingling!
この愛で、見つけた！胸がギュンギュン愛は止まらないの
With this love, found you! Love won't stop!
好き好き大好き 好き寝る メリミー ふたりだけの愛の巣から もう逃がさないずっと
From our exclusive love nest, never letting you escape!
永遠の愛を誓いましょう 神様さえキューを跳ねるよ
Let's swear eternal love, even God jumps past the cue!
我慢できないはやぎちゃお、God to heaven! 子供のなかにとらわれて
I can't hold back, God to heaven! Trapped as a child,
効率的スマートな笑顔、効率的スマイル、効率的笑顔
Efficient smart smile, efficient smile forever!
やる気がないときの、やめる時の命ある限りダブダブチュッチュッすることを誓います！
I swear to do kisses as long as I live!
世界で一番愛してるよ
I love you more than anyone in the world!
ベイビーもう私をひとり人にしないであなたがないとだめなのさびしがりあんな
Baby, don't leave me alone, I need you so much!
私のそばにいてずっとみんなとも愛してるよ
Stay by my side forever, I love everyone too!
胸がギュンギュン愛は止まらないの好き好き大好き好きめぷりー
My heart is pounding, love won't stop!
私だけの お姫様 もう離さないずっと
My only princess, I'll never let you go!
境界で意識を上げましょう 神様だって怖くない
Let's raise consciousness, even God isn't scary!
思い立ったが吉日じゃ お嫁に何卒チュッ！
Whenever you decide is lucky, please make me your bride!
ありがとうガリー
Thank you, Gally!
ドキドキ… 胸キュン・ルージュ？ Let's go！
Heart-pounding... heart-throbbing rouge? Let's go!
ないない足りないないない
No, no, not enough, no, no
ないない船からないない
No, no, from the ship, no, no
手には帰られない 前にオワタ
Can't go back to my hands, it's already over
演ったら今度ユーロ 万年出勤出勤
If you do it, next is Euro, working forever
ルッピャリラ、旺言堂、満員ファイト
Luppyarira, Ougendo, packed fight
寄ってらっしゃい 寄ったら おいでな社長様
Come on in, if you stop by, welcome Mr. President
お宝売り忘れんな レッツゴーアクション
Don't forget to sell your treasure, let's go action
どこのハート
Whose heart?
オンボロパーカー
Shabby hoodie
クリッピングに眼帯は使用済み
Clipping and eyepatch are already used
How much? いくらからの一億円！
How much? Starting from 100 million yen!
マリンの声
Marine's voice
How much?
いくらからの一億円！
Starting from 100 million yen!
ぶっ飛んで、コンセージュ
Blown away, concierge
欲しいの欲しいの無い？ 万人に助けて欲しいの？
Want it, want it, isn't there? Do you want everyone to help?
最終情事
Ultimate affair
ほにまにバレー、バレー、バレー、バレー
Honestly ballet, ballet, ballet, ballet
パレパレパレパレ パレパレパレパレ
Pare-pare pare-pare pare-pare!
売り出せやお宝 とっぱとっぱとっぱっぱ！
Sell out your treasure, toppa-toppa-toppappa!
可愛いでもっちゅーき恋、勝利にこーりー
Cute yet heart-pounding love, victory in the ice
なんてね、ダラダラ欲望絡ませ
Just kidding, intertwining lazy desires
ペラペラ本音満たされ、ショキショキラッキー乞い
Flipping through true feelings fulfilled, snip-snip asking for luck
ぐるぐる世界が回されて、スーパーチャージングな夜はハンピサワー！
The world spins round and round, a supercharging night is a happy hour!
いざHammer aaaaaan! Congratulations!
Now, Hammer aaaaaan! Congratulations!
演ったら今度ユーロ 万年出勤出勤
If you do it, next is Euro, working forever
ルッピャリラ、旺言堂、満員ファイト
Luppyarira, Ougendo, packed fight
どこがベストじゃ、れあるまるくっちゅっちょ
Where is the best, real round smacking
貝殻ほめきんぎんど、おにまにわー！
Shells praising gold and silver, demon to us!
お宝打って、ニュートンやって、おふに終わって、ハピピ
Sell treasure, do Newton, finish bathing, happy-pi
急行して、嵐にあて、バーストンきゅー
Hurry through, hit by a storm, burstone queue
なんまきでこうざみっけ、あとなこうがほりあてちゃって、大発見！
Found a lecture on nanmaki, then dug up the later craft, big discovery!
これをマリンと命名するじゃ
Name this Marine
相槌きゅ
Nodding cue
ランチのほぐ、なんぱし
Lunch hog, nanpashi
所詮スカース、また足りない
After all scares, still not enough
ナンバーヒュ、抜き出せブツ、ナンバーセン、サービス、サービス、ナンバーイチ
Number hue, pull out the stuff, number sen, service, service, number one
だぐまはぼっきの、ぎょっざっく
Daguma is boki's, gyozzaku
How much?
いくらからの一億円！
Starting from 100 million yen!
マリンの声
Marine's voice
How much?
いくらからの一億円！
Starting from 100 million yen!
ぶっ飛んで、コンセージュ
Blown away, concierge
欲しいの欲しいの無い？ 万人に助けて欲しいの？
Want it, want it, isn't there? Do you want everyone to help?
最終情事
Ultimate affair
ほにまにバレー、バレー、バレー、バレー
Honestly ballet, ballet, ballet, ballet
ドキドキして、めちゃうっちゅーきー
Heart-pounding, super chu-key
曲がり切って、行きましょう！
Go all the way round, let's go!
無罪！
Innocent!
ねぇ、いってよ、ねぇ、年齢なんて関係ないってさ
Hey, tell me, hey, that age doesn't matter
そういうめんどくさいのも含めて愛してくれないって、ねぇねぇ、いってよ、ねぇ、いってない？
That you'll love me including those troublesome things, hey hey, tell me, didn't you say that?
うん、そういうこと言うんだ。
Yeah, you say things like that.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど。
By the way, on this ship, the "Beautiful Girl Innocent" rule applies, though.
流させて、魔法では逆らえない、秘密の素顔は君にだけ
Let it flow, magic cannot defy, my secret true face is only for you
特別ですよ、あかしや、さいごよ
It's special, Akashi, final
港なんてじゃ、みなととなんちゃじゃ
Ports and things, ports and whatever
騒がないわ、地殻ごろまで
I won't make a fuss, until the crust
助からの、島にしてほしい気持ち十分ならさ
From help, if the feeling of wanting it to be an island is enough
天使になっちゃえば、大人に、なっちゃう
If you become an angel, you become an adult
急かせて、びびらしゃ、でんちゃ、きみの一番で、なじんでよ、ぞろ
Hurry up, frighten them, tram, get used to being your number one
本当は自信ないけど、がんばっちゃ
Actually I'm not confident, but I'll try my best
きゅきゅきゅるんきゅきゅきゅるんるん、さいず、すん、きもち、じゅうぶん、ならさ
Kyu kyu kyurun kyu kyu kyurunrun, size, sun, if feelings are enough
天使になっちゃえば、大人に、なっちゃう
If you become an angel, you become an adult
ドキドキして、めちゃうっちゅーきー
Heart-pounding, super chu-key
お許しをだって、このマリンの
Please forgive me, because of this Marine's
魅力、魔力、ふところよく
Charm, magic, deep pockets
罪な女ね
Sinful woman
離さないで、捕まえていて、世界人のひごさ見せ付けるから
Don't let go, keep holding on, because I'll show you the majesty of the world's people
弓取らせ、ぎびさ、じゃねーか
Let her hold the bow, isn't it gibisa
君の一番でなじんでよ、ぞろ、冗談もだいすきだけど、しんけんよ
Get used to being your number one, even though I love jokes, I'm serious
きゅきゅきゅるんきゅきゅきゅるんるん、さいず、すん、きもちじゅうぶん、ならさ
Kyu kyu kyurun kyu kyu kyurunrun, size, sun, if feelings are enough
天使になっちゃえば、大人に、なっちゃう
If you become an angel, you become an adult
ドキドキして、めちゃうっちゅーきー
Heart-pounding, super chu-key
まだ早い！
Still too early!
ねぇ、いってよ、年齢なんて
Hey, tell me, age
マリンじゃなくて、マリン船長だろ！
It's not Marine, it's Captain Marine!
美少女無罪♡パイレーツ
Bishoujo Muzai♡Pirates
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
繰る繰る好奇心は森羅万象
Turning, turning, curiosity encompasses all creation
行く末神さえも知るぬ場所
Bound for a place even gods do not know
混ざり気のない情熱が澄ました空虚を逆撫でしたところ
where pure passion stirs the pristine void the wrong way,
寝付面の悪い夜も途方もないバッドニュースも
Even restless nights and endless bad news,
目まぐるしい時代も全部忘却の彼方へ笑い飛ばそう
even this dizzying era—let's laugh it all off into oblivion!
gimme that gimme that beat right now！
gimme that gimme that beat right now!
スーパーデューパーオートクチュールのシャングリラで
In the super duper haute couture Shangri-La,
日が暮れるまで踊ろうよ誰が何と言おうと気にしない
let's dance until dusk! No matter what anyone says, we don't care.
リミッター解除　そう、ただ楽しむだけ
Limiter released—yes, just having fun,
美しい声を響かせて
making our beautiful voices echo out!
yeah yeah！ yeah yeah ！ yeah yeah ！ ah-ah ah-ah
yeah yeah! yeah yeah! yeah yeah! ah-ah ah-ah
俯いた世界を変えてみせよう
Let's change this downcast world!
yeah yeah！ yeah yeah ！ yeah yeah ！ super duper
yeah yeah! yeah yeah! yeah yeah! super duper
形あるものがどうしても欲しいよ　だけど…
Even if something has form, I want it no matter what... but...
この世界を変えることはきっとできないけど
We surely can't change this world, but...
君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
inside your world, we should be able to change it!
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて何ひとつ欠かせないから
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, withering—not a single thing can be missed,
最後に君が笑ってくれればもうそれだけでいい
so if you smile at the end, that's all we need.
言葉の紡ぐ人優しさを編む人それぞれの正義をわかってあげたい
We want to understand everyone's justice—those who spin words, those who knit kindness.
絡まった矛盾と辻褄合わせそんな切なさを抱えて今日を生きて
Tangled contradictions and reconciled inconsistencies, carrying such sorrow as we live today.
言葉の紡ぐ人優しさを編む人それぞれの正義をわかってあげたい
We want to understand everyone's justice—those who spin words, those who knit kindness.
絡まった矛盾と辻褄合わせそんな切なさを抱えて今日を生きて
Tangled contradictions and reconciled inconsistencies, carrying such sorrow as we live today.
芽吹いた明かり　隣から隣へやがて一つに
A sprouting light, from neighbor to neighbor, eventually becoming one.
夜の帳や息を吹き込んだ
The curtain of night, breathing life into it.
君とじゃなきゃだめなんだ…
It has to be with you...
このまま寝てしまうにはもったいないほど…切なく込み合った夜だった
So precious that sleeping right now feels like a waste... a night choked with sorrow.
はっきり浮かび上がった夢の輪郭　それは確かに愛だった
The clearly emerging outline of a dream—it was surely love.
時計が見守る今宵の一周を辿って　煌めく星屑
Tracing tonight's single revolution watched over by the clock, gleaming stardust.
色やカタチ温度や日々不完全な僕らだけどきっと最後には
Colors, shapes, temperatures, and days—we're imperfect, but surely at the end,
本当の音で繋がってこの世界を変えることはきっとできないけど
connected by true sounds... We surely can't change this world, but...
この世界を変えることはきっとできないけど
We surely can't change this world, but...
君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
inside your world, we should be able to change it!
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて何ひとつ欠かせないから
Sprouting, blooming, bearing fruit, withering—not a single thing can be missed,
最後に君が笑ってくれればもうそれだけでいい
so if you smile at the end, that's all we need.
言葉の紡ぐ人優しさを編む人それぞれの正義をわかってあげたい
We want to understand everyone's justice—those who spin words, those who knit kindness.
絡まった矛盾と辻褄合わせそんな切なさを抱えて今日を生きて
Tangled contradictions and reconciled inconsistencies, carrying such sorrow as we live today.
みんな聴いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for listening!
楽しんでくれましたかー！
Did you enjoy it?!
ステージ4まだまだ続きます！盛り上がっていくぞー！
Stage 4 is still going! Let's keep the energy up!
ただいまー！ただいまー！
We're back! We're back!
セカンド、ステージ4、始まります！
Second Stage 4 is starting!
イェーイ！
Yay!
エピソード2、最終日だよ！まだまだいけるよなー！
Episode 2, final day! We can still keep going, right?!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ちょっとね、今歌って踊って若いのに疲れてないでーす！
Wait, we just sang and danced, but we're not tired at all!
まだまだ元気がありまーす！
We still have plenty of energy!
すごく元気だね！
You've got so much energy!
でもこんなにもさ、たくさんの声援を浴びたらさ、もうパワーもらっちゃうよね！ほんとにさ！でもまだまだね、ステージは続いていきますので皆さん、右肩上がりに…
But when we get cheered on by so many people like this, we get all filled with power! Really! But stage 2 is still continuing, everyone, ascending higher...
もっとデカい声！
Give us an even louder voice!
楽しんでるねー！
You're having fun, huh!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
じゃ、ちょっと自己紹介からさせていたきまーす！
Now, let's start with a quick self-introduction!
可愛いポジティブジニアス！
Cute and positive genius!
めっちゃ嬉しいホロライブDEV_IS
I'm so happy, hololive DEV_IS
ReGLOSSの一条莉々華だよ、こんに莉々！
ReGLOSS's Ichijou Ririka! Konriri!
ホロライブDEV_IS ReGLOSSの一条莉々華の同期の音乃瀬奏だよ～！
And hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS's Ichijou Ririka's peer, Otonose Kanade!
え、何何何？
Huh, what what what?
さっきまではさ、何して、え、ちょっとドキドキするって言ってたのに！
Until just now, you were saying you were nervous!
がんばれ！
Do your best!
ねえ、皆さん楽しんでますかー！
Hey, everyone, are you having fun?!
ペンライトも莉々華の緑にしてくれてるね、すごい、ありがとうー！
You even made your penlights Ririka's green color! That's amazing, thank you!
はい、ということで、え、もうすでに何曲か、みんなにね、お披露目できたと思うんですけれど、
Yes, so, uh, we've already debuted several songs for you all,
はい、今回ちょっとね、セブンスフェスのテーマとして、ま、Ridin' on Dreamsということで、ステージと、そして、みなさんのお客さんのね、架け橋の形がトロッコとしてね、出てきましたー！
yes, and this time, as the theme for 7th Fes, "Ridin' on Dreams," the bridge connecting the stage and you, the audience, appeared as a float!
トロッコね、ちょっと私たちも乗らせてもらったんですけど、もう本当にみんなのね、笑顔が、嬉しそうな顔が見えましたー！
We got to ride the float too, and we could really see everyone's smiles and happy faces!
見えてたよー！めっちゃ見えてたよ、顔とか持ってるグッズとか！最高！
We could see you! We could totally see your faces and the goods you were holding! Awesome!
ありがとうー！ありがとうー！
Thank you! Thank you!
あれー？
Huh?
社長、何やりたい？いや、もう1番最初の全体曲の時から、
President, what do you want to do? Well, ever since the very first overall song,
なんかみんなのね、こうかけ声とかペンライトとかが、もう、ぶわーって、ぶわーって嬉しいぐらい来て、
everyone's cheering and penlights came in a huge wave that made me so happy,
ちょっとそれを、このMC中にもちょっとやりたいんですけど、いいですか？
and I kind of want to do that during this MC too, is that okay?
いいですかー！？やったー！
Is that okay?! Yay!
え、じゃあ莉々華はペンライトを使って、ちょっとみんなと、交流したいです！いいですか皆さん、ペンライトの準備はー？
Uh, then Ririka wants to use penlights to interact with everyone! Is everyone ready with your penlights?
社長の色は緑だよー！
The president's color is green!
じゃあ、ちょっと全部を、濃いピンク、薄いピンクじゃないですよ！莉々華の濃いピンクにしてもらってもいいですかー？
So, can you make all of them hot pink—not light pink, okay? Hot pink for Ririka, is that alright?
もうできてるやん！やったー！やったー！お花畑みたい！
You've already done it! Yay! Yay! It looks like a field of flowers!
じゃあ次は、
Then next,
カナデのカラーである黄色にしてもらってもいいですかー？カナデの色もしてくれるのー？ありがとう！最高！
can you make it yellow, which is Kanade's color? You'll do Kanade's color too? Thank you! Awesome!
じゃあ次は、莉々華がピンクって言ったらピンク、黄色って言ったら黄色にしてね？できるかな？できるかな？
So next, when Ririka says pink, make it pink, when I say yellow, make it yellow, okay? Can you do it? Can you do it?
嘘だよ！あるんじゃないの？あ、ピンク戻してるよー！
Just kidding! Is there? Ah, they're switching back to pink!
あ、ず、どんどん変わってる！どんどん変わってる！ガチャガチャガチャガチャ、変わってるー！ありがとう！
It's changing more and more! It's changing! Clack clack clack clack, it's changing! Thank you!
じゃあ、好きな色ー！
Then, your favorite color!
ねえ、すごーい！お花畑みたい！ありがとうございます、とっても嬉しいです！
Hey, amazing! It looks like a field of flowers! Thank you so much, I'm so happy!
え、じゃあカナデは何やりたい？え、カナデはもうわかってると思うけど、
Uh, then what does Kanade want to do? Well, Kanade thinks you already know, but
え、カナデがちょっとこのDay3のMCとして出たということは、
uh, the fact that Kanade appeared as the MC for Day 3 means,
今日は何曜日だったかなー？
what day of the week was it today?
みんな、知ってるよねカナデが、
Everyone knows, right? Kanade,
「明日はー？」って言ったらみんなもう、生まれてきて1番のでっかい声で「月曜日ー！」って叫んでくださいね、いいですか？
when I say "Tomorrow is—?", everyone please shout "Monday!" with the loudest voice since you were born, okay?
月曜日ですよー！いきますよー！
It's Monday! Here we go!
明日はー！？月曜日ー！！
Tomorrow is—?! Monday!!
いいか！ありがとうー！
Awesome! Thank you!
いやでも、明日が月曜日でもね、そんな疲れも吹っ飛ばすぐらい今日は最高のパフォーマンスをね、みんなに届けていきますので皆さん、まだまだ
Even if tomorrow is Monday, we're going to deliver the best performance to blow away all that fatigue, so everyone, there's still...
盛り上がっていきますよ！
Let's get hyped!
おっしゃあ！
Yeah!
いいね。
Nice.
もっといけるよ！
You can do better!
まだまだいけるよ！
You can still go harder!
いけるいける！
You can do it!
最高！
Awesome!
Hey！
Hey!
ということで、あのね、今回現地に
So, you know, everyone here
来てくださっているみんなと、
at the venue today,
配信で見てくださっているみんなも…
and everyone watching the stream...
え、配信のみんなは、
Um, everyone watching the stream,
#ホロライブフェスEXPO26Day3ってポストしてね！
please post with #HololiveFesExpo26Day3!
いいね！
Nice!
そしてそして、楽しいお知らせがあるんですけど。
And, and, we have a fun announcement.
楽しいお知らせ、何？
A fun announcement, what is it?
いいね！
Nice!
YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方は、
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok,
ここまで！
up to here!
どうしよう！
What should we do!
ねえ、どうしよう！
Hey, what should we do!
はい、でもね、よかったら皆さんまだまだ
Yeah, but you know, if you'd like,
楽しいライブは続きますので！
there's still more fun concert!
応援してください！
Please cheer for us!
それではですね、次の曲に入りたいと
Now then, we'd like to move on
思いますので、「せーの」って言ったら…
to the next song, so when we say ready...
いいですか？
Are you ready?
オーケー！
Okay!
それじゃあいくよ！
Then here we go!
せーの！ Ridin' on Dreams！
Ready, go! Ridin' on Dreams!
引き続き楽しいんでね！
Keep having fun, everyone!